你用乒乓球打败迈克真的太帅了
The way you crushed Mike at Ping-Pong was such a turn-on.
你想那个吗
You wanna...?
我是想  不过我有点累了
You know, I'd love to, but I'm a little tired.
我会用枕套把头包住的
I'll put a pillowcase over my head.
走起
You're on.
-嗨  -有事吗
- Hey. - What's up?
迈克在冲凉
Well, Mike's taking a shower,
顺便说一下  我们还没有做那个
which,by the way, there's no law against.
我们想去吃点东西  所以如果你们也想...
And then we're gonna grab some food. So if you want--
-终于...  -那是罗斯吗
- Finally. - Is that Ross?
是啊  这烂墙不隔音
Yeah. You can hear everything through these stupid walls.
好象有人和他一起
Sounds like he's with someone.
也可能就他自己
He could be alone.
今天早上我听见他做俯卧撑
This morning I heard him do pushups
后来还跟他的三头肌说话
and then talk to his triceps.
等等  菲比是对的
Wait a minute, I think Phoebe's right.
我也听见有人和他在一起
Yeah, I hear someone else in there with him.
-盖勒博士  -天呐  太不可思议了
- Dr. Geller! - God, you're amazing.
都不用我说  你就这么叫了
I didn't even have to ask you to call me that.
天呐  是查莉
Oh, my God, that's Charlie!
她背着乔伊和罗斯乱搞
She's cheating on Joey with Ross!
那个尖酸刻薄的大只荡妇
Oh, that tart! Floozy! Giant!
这样做不对吧
I'm not sure about this.
是  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
这根本不关我们的事
This is none of our business.
我意思是这不是最好的偷听方法
I'm not sure it's the best way  to hear everything.
给我个玻璃杯
Some one give me a glass!
不  我不会那么做的
No, I'm not gonna do this, okay?
我不会偷听我朋友的
I'm not gonna eavesdrop on my friend.
我爱巴巴多斯
I love Barbados.
我不敢相信我在吻你
I can't believe I'm kissing you.
我在吻瑞秋啊
I'm kissing Rachel!
我知道  我就是她
I know. I'm her.
瑞秋和乔伊  是瑞秋和乔伊
Rachel and Joey! It's Rachel and Joey!
-什么  -过来这边
- What? - Get over here!
噢  天呐  墙薄点太好了
Oh, my God! I love how thin these walls are!
谢谢
Thank you.
之前你说我们是不可能的
Hey, before, you said that nothing could happen
为什么又改变主意了
between us. What changed?
之前这样说是因为罗斯
Well, I only said that because of Ross.
可后来我看见他在吻查莉
And then I saw him kissing Charlie.
什么
What?
罗斯和查莉
Ross and Charlie?
她真的很想
Wow! She's really making her way
加入到我们中来呢
through the group, huh?
-我干嘛干预人家这个  -是啊
- Eh, who am I to talk?  - Yeah.
真不敢相信  瑞秋和乔伊
I can't believe this. Rachel and Joey?
那边那对恐龙二人组
How about the dinosaur twins
还没人管
in the other room?
-那堵墙没人负责啊  -我来
- No one is manning that wall! - I'm on it!
-听到什么了  -他们好像把窗帘拉上了
- Anything?  - I think I hear curtains closing.
我们这边已经把鞋子踢掉了
We've got shoes being kicked off over here.
弹簧床  不会错的
Bedsprings! Unmistakable!
你有想过那是你哥吗
You realize that's your brother.
你说出来才想到  来换我
Not until you said it. Somebody switch!
等等
Wow! Wait a minute.
罗斯和查莉  乔伊和瑞秋
Ross and Charlie. Joey and Rachel.
菲比和迈克
Phoebe and Mike.
我们是唯一没有换过人的一对呢
We're the only ones leaving with the person we came with!
我和莫妮卡一起来的
That's not true. I came with Monica,
却要和古怪阿尔一起走
I'm leaving with Weird Al.
好吧  我受够了这种头发的笑话了
Okay, I've had it with the hair jokes.
明天早上我们走之前我会去发廊的
Tomorrow I'm going to the salon.
好的荞麦人
Okay, Buckwheat.
你们该来听听这个
You gotta hear this,
爽啊  简直就像是免费的A片
it's great! It's like free porn.
怎么啦
Is everything okay?
只是...我觉得不能这么做
It's just-- I don't think I can do this.
是怕床单上有东西吗
Oh, is it because of what might be on the bedspread?
我也看过那些报道了  在红外线下...
I saw that report, with the infrared--
不  不
No! No.
不
No.
我要跟乔伊谈谈
Look, I need to talk to Joey.
你们才刚刚分手
I mean, you guys just broke up.
我们之间有进展前
Before anything more happens between us,
我要确定他不反对
I need to know he's okay with it.
我完全理解
I completely understand.
好吧  我去找他
All right, I'm gonna go find him.
我需要点时间  让我那个...
I just need a second before I can, you know....
外婆...
Grandma...
-好了  过会儿见  -好的
- Okay, I'll see you later. - Okay!
关门了  他走了
That's the door. He's gone.
她...打开了电视...
And she's turning on the TV...
在看...《选美特工》
...and watching Miss Congeniality.
亲爱的  如果你隔着墙
Honey? If you know it
都能知道那是什么  那你也看太多了
through a wall, you know it too well.
嘿  你们干什么呢
Hey, what are you guys doing?
我们...快要走了  都很伤心
We're just-- We're sad to go,
所以在跟这旅馆告别
so we're  just saying goodbye to the hotel.
我爱你
I love you
天堂旅馆  高尔夫胜地还有水疗
Paradise Hotel Golf Resort and Spa.
对  我们玩得很开心  谢谢
Yeah. We had a great time, thank you.
再见
Bye.
好吧  你们看见乔伊了吗
Okay. Hey, have you guys seen Joey anywhere?
他应该在他房间里
He's probably in his room
和他现任女友查莉在一起
with his current girlfriend, Charlie.
这是目前我们了解的情况
That's the situation as we know it.
如果看到他
If you see him,
告诉他我在找他好吗
could you tell him I'm looking for him?
-没问题  -谢了
- You got it.  - Thanks.
谢谢你
Thank you.
另一边墙  同志们  另一边
Other wall, people! Other wall!
瑞秋  在吗
Rach, you there?
天呐  是罗斯啊
Oh, my God, that's Ross!
怎么办
What are we gonna do?
噢  保...持冷静
Okay, just be calm.
让他感觉  我们只是在聊天
For all he knows, we're just hanging out.
好吗   随意一点
All right? So just be nonchalant.
这不叫随意
That's not nonchalant!
我都不知道你说的啥意思
No idea what it means.
好吧  躲起来
Okay, just hide.
-瑞秋  -来了  试试床下行不行
- Rach?  - Coming! Try under the bed.
床底下没空间
There's no room under the bed
-没事吧  -没事
- Is everything okay?  - Yeah.
-嘿  你知道乔伊在那儿吗  - 嗨...
- Hey. Do you know where Joey is?  - Hi.
我真的不知道
I really don't.
我能和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a minute?
当然  可以
Yeah. Sure.
我简直不敢相信  你们一直...
I don't believe this. Have you guys been--?
墙这边  只能听不许说话
This is the listening side of the wall.
然后她告诉我
Then she told me
她和乔伊已经分手了
that she and Joey had broken up
某程度上是因为她喜欢我
and part of the reason was she had feelings for me.
是吧  好
Right. Yeah.
你知道我碰到查莉的那天
You know I've wanted to ask Charlie out
就想跟她约会
since the day I met her.
噢  我明白...
Oh, I know, I know.
我知道你这些天来很难过
That's been really hard for you.
总之  事情一件接一件
Anyway, one thing led to another, and...
还没反应过来  我们已经在接吻了
...before you know it, we were kissing.
你觉得乔伊会多生气
How angry do you think Joey's gonna be?
这很难说  罗斯
That is hard to say, Ross.
这很难说
That is hard to say.
我要去找他了
I gotta find him.
他一定就在这什么地方
He's gotta be here someplace.
就是啊
You would think.
乔伊
Joey?
-他走了吗  -你怎么做到的
- Is he gone?  - How are you doing this?
怎么  你们
What? Hey!
你们怎么...  这是怎么回事
What are you--? What is this?
你们一直在偷听吗
Have you been listening this entire time?
对
Yeah!
那  这又是怎么回事
Now, what is this?
这是怎么回事  这么说吧
What is this? Well, let's see.
我们吻了十分钟
We kissed for 10 minutes...
然后和朋友说这件事
...and now we're talking to our friends about it,
只有六年级学生才这样
so I guess this is sixth grade.
不  你们想过这会使
No, no. Have you thought about
事情变得多复杂吗
how complicated this could get?
罗斯怎么办
What about Ross?
可他现在跟查莉在一起
Look, he's with Charlie now.
对  可他想在正式开始之前
Yeah, but he wants to talk to you
先和你说一下
before anything really happens with her.
作为朋友
And as his friend,
你们不觉得
I mean, don't you think
你们也应该这么做吗
he deserves the same from you?
你太讨厌了  姓盖勒的
You're a pain in my ass, Geller.
好吧  各位
All right, you guys.
很感谢你们的意见
Look, we appreciate all the advice...
但这是我和乔伊之间的事
...but this is between Joey and me.
我们能处理
And I think We can handle it.
我们可以回去
We'll go.
可你能为我们这些
Will you do one thing for us,
在乎你的朋友做件事吗
the people that care about you?
-当然  -去说清楚
- Sure.  - Enunciate.
出去
Get out!
他们说得对吗
Are they right?
可能吧  是  我是说
Probably, yeah. I mean, maybe we should
我们应该先和罗斯说清楚
hold off until we talk to Ross.
对  我们可以等
Yeah. Yeah. We can wait.
我们可以今天晚上什么事都不做
We don't have to do anything tonight.
对  我想这样最好
Yeah, I think that would be best.
那我要...我要走了
So, I'm gonna-- I'm gonna take off.
-虽然...  -我喜欢"虽然"
- Although--  - I like "although."
我是说
I mean, you know....
我和罗斯已经有将近
Ross and I haven't dated in, like...
六年没约会了
...six years.
六年
Six years?
哇...跟读高中一样久了
Wow. That's almost as long as high school.
而且  他现在跟查莉在一起
Plus, you know, he is with Charlie now.
就是啊
Absolutely.
-他想的不是你  -是啊
- He's not thinking about you.  - No.
我想的才是你
I'm thinking about you.
对
Yeah.
-我们忘了罗斯吧  -已经忘了
- Let's forget about Ross.  - It's forgotten.
-怎么了  -没事
- What's wrong?  - Nothing.
说真的  怎么了
Seriously, what is it?
没事  真的...
Nothing. It's really...
没事  再来...
it's nothing. Come here...
怎么了
What's wrong?
对不起  我只是...
Sorry, I just...
看起来我无法忽略罗斯
I can't seem to get Ross out of my head.
好吧  让我来帮你
Well, maybe I can help.
你的唇真软  再来一次
Your lips are so soft. Do that again.
你说得对  我们真的要先跟罗斯谈谈
Yeah, we need to talk to Ross. Yeah.
嗨  你们准备好要走了吗
Hey. You guys ready to go?
还没  莫妮卡还在发廊
Not quite. Monica's at the salon,
而我还没收拾好
and I'm just finishing packing.
伙计  你不打算带上圣经吗
Dude, you're not taking your Bible?
你不应该拿这个走的
You're not supposed to take that.
而且这是新约
Besides, it's a New Testament.
你要它干什么
What are you gonna do with it?
了解耶稣
Learn about Jesus.
-嗨  -你跟乔伊说过了
- Hey!  - So did you talk to Joey?
没  我找不到他
No. I couldn't find him.
我会在飞机上跟他说
I'm just gonna talk to him on the plane.
好吧  好主意  盖勒博士
Okay. Sounds like a good idea, Dr. Geller.
少来了
Stop it.
大..."勃"...士...
Ph.D.
你真淫荡
You're filthy.
嘿  你们见过莫妮卡了吗
Hey. Have you guys seen Monica?
她去发廊了吧
Actually, I think she went to the salon.
对  她确实去了发廊
Oh, yeah. Oh, she went to the salon, all right.
看看
Check it out!
给某人的生活添姿添彩啊
Whose day just got better?
钱德勒
Chandler!
嘿
Hey!
-你觉得怎么样  -我想...
- What do you think?  - I think...
我想我能看见你的头皮
I think I can see your scalp.
很喜欢吧
Don't you just love it?
对...  你把贝壳挂在头上
Yeah. Yeah, you got shellfish in your head.
了不起  向上吧  少年
It's something. You go, girlfriend.
-你以前没这么说过  对吧  -一次没有
- You never said that in your life. - Not once.
我想也是
I thought so.
噢  听着
Oh, and listen to this.
没想到  这不光是视觉的享受
What do you know? It's a treat for the eyes
也是听觉的
and the ears.
我和查莉分手后
Wow, it's kind of weird that
还要坐在她旁边  太奇怪了
I'm sitting next to Charlie after we broke up.
就是说  巴巴多斯航空
Yeah. It's almost as if Air Barbados
真是不关心你的私生活
doesn't care about your social life.
有人想替我
Does someone mind switching
跟查莉坐吗
and sitting with Charlie?
伙计...
Oh, I mean, l-- Dude,
我跟查莉整个会议都在一起了
I spent the whole conference with Charlie.
- 我了解  - 不  我要的
- I understand.  - No, I'll do it.
我要能跟谁换换就好了
Wish I could switch.
我真的不想
I really don't want to
跟阿伦·艾佛森坐在那儿
sit with Allen lverson over there.
飞机起飞
Once we're in the air
机长关闭系好安全带的标志后
and the captain turns off the seat belt sign
你就可以自由的在我的"机舱"里遨游了
...you feel free to roam about my cabin.
你检查行李箱的时候
And you should be careful
要小心
when checking your overhead bins.
很容易和别人的搞混的...
Because items may shift during--
这个你不在行
Oh, you're not good at this.
今晚你没必要非得回家  对吧
You don't have to go home tonight, do you?
不  我想我可以来过夜的
Yea, I think I can come over.
今天星期六  不是吗
It's Saturday, right?
怎么了
What?
今晚我不行
I can't do anything tonight.
为什么不行
Why not?
我有约会
I have a date.
你有个...你有个约会  跟谁
You have a...you have a date? With who?
是...我女朋友
Oh, it's my girlfriend.
-你有...你有女朋友  -对
- You have...you have a girlfriend?  - Yeah.
之前我们分手后
Well, when you and I broke up,
我开始跟其他人约会
I started seeing someone.
-那...多久了  -3个月
- Well, for how long?  - Three months.
3个月
Three months?
好吧
Okay.
这可能不关我的事
This is none of my business,
但是你还想跟她好多久
but how long are you gonna keep seeing her?
今天晚饭的时候  我会告诉她结束了
I'll tell her that it's over tonight at dinner.
我保证
I promise.
好  好吧  那你去吧
Oh, okay, good. You do that.
当你回到家
When you get home,
可能会有个特别的邮包
maybe there'll be a special delivery package
在那儿等着你
waiting for you.
我可能会签收  撕开它
Maybe I'll sign for it, tear it open.
扯开包装材料...
Pull out the packing material--
你知道吗  我们会做爱
You know what. We'll have sex.
你不用再说了
Let's leave it there.
我要去和乔伊谈了
All right, I'm gonna go talk to Joey.
我想现在时机很好
I think this is the right time.
空姐说完"免税"以后他总是情绪很好
He's in a good mood after the flight attendant says "duty-free."
好  祝你好运
Okay. Good luck.
罗斯要过来了
Ross is coming over.
我想现在会是告诉他的好时机
I think now would be a good time to talk to him.
我想是的  只是...我好紧张啊
I guess so. I'm just--I'm really nervous.
好吧  你这样想  你说完以后
Well, keep in mind that by the time you're done...
他们就上餐了
...they'll probably be serving dinner.
还紧张吗
Still nervous?
我要吃打卤面
I'm gonna get the lasagna.
-嗨  瑞秋 -怎么
- Hey, Rach?  - Yeah?
介意我在这儿坐一会吗
Do you mind if I sit here for a sec?
不介意  当然不  不
Yeah. Yeah, sure. Yeah.
祝你好运
Good luck.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hey.  - Hey.
我  呃...
So l...
有点儿关于查莉的事要跟你说
I kind of need to talk to you about Charlie.
怎么
Yeah?
昨天晚上你们俩分手以后...
Last night, after you guys broke up....
当然我觉得很遗憾
So sorry to hear about that, by the way.
查莉和我倾诉  然后...
Well, Charlie and I were talking, and...
你们接吻了
You kissed.
什...么
Wh-- What?
你怎么会这样想的啊
What? What would give you that idea?
-我看见了  -对  我们是接吻了
- I saw you.  - Yeah, we kissed.
不过…什么都没发生
But nothing else.
知道吗
Nothing else happened, okay?
-罗斯...没关系的  -什么
- Ross...It's okay.  - What?
这没关系
It's okay. You know, look...
我完全理解  好吗  你们...
...l totally understand, all right? You guys...
在一起比我跟她在一起更合适
...make way more sense than her and I ever did, you know?
而且……
And....
-我希望你幸福  -真的
- I want you to be happy. - Are you serious?
当然
Yeah.
-我也有点事想说...  -我真是无话可说了
- Now I have something--  - I am speechless.
我是说  你居然把
I mean, the fact that you would
我的幸福放在第一位
put my happiness first like that, I mean....
你真是个令人难以置信的好朋友
You're an incredible friend,
你知道吗
do you know that?
-呃...在你...  -不  我说真的
- Well, look, before you go--  - No, I mean it.
你既忠诚
I mean, you're so loyal, man.
又无私  慷慨...
And selfless and generous.
我是  当然是
I am those things, yeah.
我认识钱德勒更久
I've known Chandler longer,
一直认为他我最好的朋友
so I think of him as my best friend. But now...
不过现在  我得重新考虑一下了
...l may have to rethink some stuff.
伙计
Dude!
如果有任何事情我能帮忙的...
Hey, if there is ever anything I can do for you....
暂时还想不到
I can't think of anything.
-谢谢  -没什么
- Thanks.  - Yeah.
-嗨  -嗨
- So hi.  - Hi.
你和乔伊谈过了
So you talked to Joey?
对  我们聊得很开心
Oh, yeah. We had a really good talk.
-噢  太棒了  -对
- Oh, that's great.  - Yeah.
那一切都没问题吧
So everything's okay?
没问题  简直太棒了
Oh, no, it's great.
很棒  他真是好得让人吃惊
It's great. He's an amazing guy.
很显然  我也这么想
Oh, well, obviously, I think so too.
对  我感到很兴奋
Well, I'm so excited about this.
真的  兴奋
Really? Excited?
你开玩笑吗
What, are you kidding?
我做梦都在想着要去干那事
I have had some very dirty dreams about this.
让开
Excuse me.
你没说  是吗
You didn't tell him, did you?
我没法说
I couldn't.
他把我说得天花乱坠
He was saying all these really nice things about me.
我不想惹火他
I didn't want him to get mad
让他收回那些话
and take them back.
我快要顶替钱德勒的位置了
I'm gonna edge out Chandler!
好吧  乔伊
Fine. Yon know what Joey. Forget it.
回纽约以后  我跟他说
When we go back to New York, I will tell him.
谢谢  真的  我跟感激
Thank you. Yeah, I appreciate that.
-你好  迈克家  -我是迈克
- Hi, Mike's place.  - Hey, it's Mike.
-真快  -不是  她还没来
- That was fast.  - Oh, no, she's not here yet.
我想我应该离开
You know, I'm just gonna take off
然后在电话上跟她说分手就好
and break up with her over the phone.
你不能这样
You can't do that. Oh, come on,
这样太怂了  迈克
Mike, strap on a pair.
怎么不直接告诉她我们又复合了
Why don't you tell her that we got back together.
女人欣赏诚实
You know, women appreciate honesty.
偶尔也喜欢
We also appreciate gentle spanking
被轻柔地打屁股
once in a while, just FYl.
还有一件事
One more thing.
在我的咖啡台上有张宝宝的照片
There might be a picture of Precious on my coffee table.
她叫宝宝
Her name's Precious?
她是纯种的吗
Is she a pure breed,
还是你在动物收容所捡来的
or did you pick her up at the pound?
总之  我只想提醒你一下
Any way, I just want to give you a heads up.
好  如果她不高兴了
Okay. And if she gets upset.
记得挠挠她的肚子
...just scratch her tummy
逗她高兴
and give her a liver snap.
嗨  我是宝宝  你是谁
Hi. I'm Precious. Who are you?
-我是菲比  -菲比
- I'm Phoebe.  - Phoebe?
迈克的前女友菲比
Mike's ex-girlfriend, Phoebe?
他的一生挚爱  那个菲比
The love of his life? That Phoebe?
我真想让同事们快点看看这个
Oh, I can't wait for everyone at work to see these!
明天晚上你才回去工作  是吗
You go back to work tomorrow night?
对
Yeah.
那么如果你想让他们看
So if you want people to see them...
也就是说你破晓前不会把他们解下啦
...you're not having them taken out, say, at the break of dawn?
如果我解下来了
Well, if I had them taken out,
我就不能这么做了
then I wouldn't be able to do this.
你很喜欢  对吧
You like that, right?
你唱什么呢
What are you singing?
《十全十美》里的波利乐舞曲
It's "Bolero" from 10.
那是《现代启示录》里的《狂热的瓦格纳》
It's "Ride of the Valkyries" from Apocalypse Now.
是这样  梳辫子是
Here's the thing. The cornrows were
用来解决你头发的卷曲问题的
a solution to your frizzy-hair problem.
现在到家了
Now that we're home,
没有那样的困扰了
you don't have that problem.
所以如果你考虑一下...
If you think about it...
我讨厌他们
I hate them.
什么  你说过你喜欢的
What? You said you liked them.
我说过吗  我们回想一下
Did l? Let's refresh.
我想我的原话是
I believe what I said was
"我可以看见你的头皮"
that I could see your scalp.
好吧  虽然你不喜欢
Well, fine. So you don't like them.
可其他人都喜欢
Everybody else does.
再一次  让我们回到那次旅游
Again, let's journey back.
我记得瑞秋说的是
As I recall, Rachel said
她以前从没注意过你的头骨的形状
she had never noticed the shape of your skull before.
还有乔伊...
And Joey?
乔伊当时看不出你有什么不一样
Well, Joey didn't realize there was anything different.
我不管  我喜欢这样
You know what? I don't care.
喜欢它  而且我要留着它
I like it like this, and I'm gonna keep it.
你嫉妒是
You're just jealous
因为你的头发不能这么做
because your hair can't do this.
-敲在你的牙上了  -还有眼睛
- Get yourself in the tooth? - And the eye.
她来了  艾玛
Hi! There she is! Hi, Emma.
天呐  我想死你了
Oh, my God, I missed you.
艾玛  我真是太想你了
Oh, Emma, I missed you so much. Hi.
你和外婆过得开心吗  呃
Did you have a good time with Grandma Green? Huh?
她喋喋不休的时候
Did she give you a bottle of antidepressants again
给你抗抑郁药了吗
to use as a rattle?
只有一次  罗斯
That was one time, Ross,
而且只有5毫克
and they were only, like, five milligrams.
艾玛  爸爸有礼物带给你  知道吗
Hey, Emma, Daddy has some presents for you, okay?
我想让你在这儿等一会儿
I want you to wait right here.
在这  宝贝儿
Come here, sweetie.
罗斯  我有点儿事
Ross, actually, there's something that
要跟你说
I really need to talk to you about.
好的  说吧
Okay, shoot.
-好吧  好的  事情是这样的  -哦不
- Okay. All right, here's the deal.  - Oh, no!
怎么了
What is it?
大瓶的洗发液破了
Oh, major shampoo explosion!
听着罗斯  这很难开口
Look, Ross, this really isn't easy.
还沾得到处都是
Oh, it's all over everything!
为什么  为什么偏偏是我
Why? Why me?
因为你拿了300瓶洗发液
Because you took 300 bottles of shampoo?
对不起  对不起  你刚才说什么
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You were saying?
好吧...  是关于我和...
Well, yeah. Look, it's about me and--
噢  不要  又一瓶
Oh, not another one!
天呐  是摩丝
Oh, my--Oh, and this is moisturizer!
这个更难清理
It's even harder to clean!
为什么
Why?
为什么坏事总是落到好人的头上
Why do bad things happen to good people?
好吧  很显然我来得不是时候
Wow. Clearly this is not a good time.
你觉得呢
You think?
好的  再见
Okay. Bye.
好了  迈克已经回来了
All right, so Mike's on his way over.
你以为你们在这儿见
You thought you were meeting here,
他却以为在餐馆见面
he thought at the restaurant, so....
谁对谁错不重要
It doesn't matter who's right or wrong.
重要的是我要走了
The point is, I'm gonna take off.
你告诉我到底发生了什么之前
Wait. I'm not letting you leave
我不会让你走的
until you tell me what's going on here.
我是说
I mean...
你们和好了还是怎么的
...are you guys getting back together or something?
好吧
All right.
苏茜  我能叫你苏茜吗
Susie-- Can I call you Susie?
我叫宝宝
My name is Precious.
我可叫不出口
I can't say that.
苏茜  跟你直说了吧
Susie, I'm gonna be straight with you.
迈克跟我确实和好了
Mike and I are back together.
并且不幸的是
And unfortunately...
这样就要终结你们的关系
...that effectively ends your relationship with him.
并且他对此感到很抱歉
He's very sorry about that,
并祝你好运
and wishes you the best luck in all your endeavors.
我无法相信  为什么
I just can't believe this. Why?
这个我也不知...
Well, I don't--
他为什么这么做
Why would he do this?
我做错什么了
What's wrong with me?
没有  你什么也没做错
There's nothing wrong with you.
那我现在到底该怎么办
What the hell am I supposed to do now?
可恶  女人  振作起来
Damn it, woman! Pull yourself together!
看在上帝的份上  保持你的尊严
Have some pride, for the love of God!
好吧  你好象不喜欢苦涩的爱情
Okay, not a fan of the tough love.
我真不敢相信
I just can't believe
迈克竟然没有给我一点暗示
that Mike didn't give me any warning.
他之前也不知道
He didn't know.
他也不是计划来巴巴多斯
He wasn't planning on coming to Barbados
向我求婚的
and proposing to me.
他向你求婚了
He proposed to you?
这真是史上最糟糕的生日了
This is the worst birthday ever!
听着  宝宝...
Look, Precious...
你不值得为迈克伤心
Mike's not worth this.
你是个迷人聪明的女孩
You're an attractive intelligent woman...
面对现实吧  迈克太不是东西了
...and let's face it, Mike's kind of a wang.
他向我求婚的同时还跟你在一起
He proposed to me while he was still seeing you.
他居然想在你生日的时候跟你分手
He was gonna break up with you on your birthday?
我本来也不想炫耀
I don't like to kiss and tell,
不过这个周末他对你不忠的太多了
but he cheated on you a lot this weekend.
天呐  可能你说对了
Oh, my God, you know, maybe you're right.
可能我并不需要他
Maybe I don't need him.
我应该受到尊重
I deserve to be treated with respect.
去你的  迈克
Screw you, Mike.
你这个胆怯的杂种
You're a coward and a bastard,
我希望你烂死在地狱里
and I hope you rot in hell!
不用谢我
You're welcome.
亲爱的  你在里面好久了
Honey? You've been in there for a long time.
没事吧
Is everything okay?
不
Not really.
我有点问题
I have a problem.
是吗  怎么了
Really? What happened?
好吧  我唱着《女人不哭》跳舞...
Well, I was dancing around and singing "No Woman, No Cry" ...
然后就挂住了
...and I got stuck.
一点都动不了了
You can't move at all?
噢  我可以动...
Oh, I can move.
如果我解开你
If I untangle you,
你会解开这个稻穗头
will you please get rid of the cornrows?
好吧
I guess so.
有些看起来有磨痕了
Some of these look a little frayed.
对  我本来想咬开的
Yeah, I tried to gnaw myself free.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
-怎么样  你跟罗斯说了吗  -没有  我想说
- So? Did you tell Ross?  - Well, I tried...
但他的洗发液出事故了
...but then he had a shampoo-related emergency.
-所以我想该轮到你去了  -不...
- So I guess now it's your turn again.  - No...
最好是你去告诉他
I think it's better if you tell him.
女人来说容易些
You know, it's easier for a woman.
你知道  如果他抓狂了  你就可以
That way, you know, if he gets mad, all you have to do is go
我不是有意的
I didn't mean it.
我太抱歉了
I'm so sorry
对  女人是这样啊
Yeah, 'cause that's what we do.
好吧...这样怎么样  明天...
Alright, alright, okay, uhm... How about this? Tomorrow...
明天我们一起去
Tomorrow we'll both go
一起告诉他
and we'll tell him together.
好吧  听起来公平些
Okay, that sounds fair.
可这样我们又不能...
That just means, once again, we can't--
我知道...
I know...
不过没问题
That's okay.
我们有自制力
I mean, we can control ourselves.
我们不是动物啊
We're not animals.
-当然  我们可以等  -是啊
- No! Of course, we can wait.  - Yeah.
那么我想该说晚安了
All right, so I guess that means good night then.
好的  晚安
Yep. Good night.
晚...安
Good night.
晚安
说真的  晚安
Seriously, good night.
别说晚安了
Stop saying good night.
真对不起啊...
I'm so sorry.
看我在抽屉里找到了什么
Look what I found in the drawer.
你还说我永远不会戴它呢
And you said I'd never wear this.
我把你解救下来
Now that I untangled you,
你还没报答我呢
how about you do a little something for me?
当然  你想让我怎么报答
Sure. What did you have in mind?
你应该知道的啊
I think you know.
真的  但我有点不想啊
Really? I don't-- I don't really feel like it.
我就是想要
This is what I want to do.
好吧
Okay.
我不知道你为什么这么喜欢它
I just don't get why you like it so much.
她是个联调局特工
She's a FBI agent,
伪装去选美
posing as a beauty contestant.